[{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980247748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12587,"timeElapsed":69247},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980254555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6803,"timeElapsed":76055},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10163,"timeElapsed":86222},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980269450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4724,"timeElapsed":90950},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980274176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4720,"timeElapsed":95675},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3191,"timeElapsed":98871},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3982,"timeElapsed":102858},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980292498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11136,"timeElapsed":113998},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980297569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":5064,"timeElapsed":119068},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11365,"timeElapsed":132933},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4229,"timeElapsed":137167},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6440,"timeElapsed":143613},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":146737},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2720,"timeElapsed":149460},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3281,"timeElapsed":152748},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3227,"timeElapsed":155979},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12553,"timeElapsed":168535},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4892,"timeElapsed":173432},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980361009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":7982,"timeElapsed":182509},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6846,"timeElapsed":189360},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":16635,"timeElapsed":206000},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3008,"timeElapsed":209011},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":212179},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6650,"timeElapsed":218833},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3051,"timeElapsed":221890},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4901,"timeElapsed":226795},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":230240},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5567,"timeElapsed":237331},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6156,"timeElapsed":243492},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980425973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3977,"timeElapsed":247473},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4444,"timeElapsed":251923},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":18637,"timeElapsed":270565},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980452035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2965,"timeElapsed":273535},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":275962},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460583,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6118,"timeElapsed":282083},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7875,"timeElapsed":289961},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4737,"timeElapsed":294703},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8676,"timeElapsed":305285},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":308239},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3868,"timeElapsed":312111},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":315189},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":317878},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":320507},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2597,"timeElapsed":323109},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3122,"timeElapsed":326237},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2330,"timeElapsed":328571},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6683,"timeElapsed":336503},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3241,"timeElapsed":339749},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521465,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3211,"timeElapsed":342965},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4893,"timeElapsed":347862},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3330,"timeElapsed":351195},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3491,"timeElapsed":354691},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2048,"timeElapsed":356743},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2729,"timeElapsed":359477},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3346,"timeElapsed":362829},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":365714},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5218,"timeElapsed":372091},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980553715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3120,"timeElapsed":375215},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5061,"timeElapsed":380280},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3879,"timeElapsed":384163},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3536,"timeElapsed":387703},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2346,"timeElapsed":390054},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3819,"timeElapsed":393877},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3155,"timeElapsed":397037},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":400031},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7871,"timeElapsed":419973},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4641,"timeElapsed":424619},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7977,"timeElapsed":432602},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2892,"timeElapsed":435498},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2812,"timeElapsed":438312},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":440537},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2328,"timeElapsed":442871},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5148,"timeElapsed":448023},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4646,"timeElapsed":452673},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":458418},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3875,"timeElapsed":462298},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6130,"timeElapsed":468432},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3161,"timeElapsed":471595},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2314,"timeElapsed":473914},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3300,"timeElapsed":477218},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2276,"timeElapsed":479499},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":482660},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3529,"timeElapsed":486191},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9422,"timeElapsed":496623},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3766,"timeElapsed":500393},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9782,"timeElapsed":510179},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3350,"timeElapsed":513533},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2376,"timeElapsed":515914},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":518461},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2180,"timeElapsed":520646},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3103,"timeElapsed":523754},{"subjectID":"bodex7wfpd","prolificID":"55b249bdfdf99b28e3c14b05","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b247782f9600cfc3a54b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3450,"timeElapsed":527209}]